export default data = [
  {
      question: "Chris: Which ______ looks better on me? Penny: I think purple’s better. You look great in purple",
      options: ["color","grade","shape","size"],
      correct_option: "color"
  },
  {
      question: "My cat got excited when it saw the boy ______ the birds",
      options: ["catches","catching","to catch","caught"],
      correct_option: "catching"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Jackson is a very ______ writer; people of all ages enjoy his stories",
      options: ["polite","popular","handsome","honest"],
      correct_option: "popular"
  },
  {
      question: "Carol sounded happy when we talked on the phone; I could feel joy in her ______",
      options: ["eyes","mail","smile","voice"],
      correct_option: "voice"
  },
  {
      question: "Mark studies very hard and never ______ classes. He goes to school even when he is sick",
      options: ["loses","misses","changes","forgets"],
      correct_option: "misses"
  },
  {
      question: "Have you got anything for Joe ______? He’d be happy to get your gift on his birthday",
      options: ["almost","either","soon","yet"],
      correct_option: "yet"
  },
  {
      question: "Susan bought ______ bread in the supermarket, but she did not buy anything to drink",
      options: ["many","some","any","one"],
      correct_option: "some"
  },
  {
      question: "Playing sports at least three times a week ______ good for your health",
      options: ["is","are","has","have"],
      correct_option: "is"
  },
  {
      question: "My parents have different hobbies. One enjoys baking; ______ enjoys taking pictures",
      options: ["another","the next","the other","the second"],
      correct_option: "the other"
  },
  {
      question: "My mom told me to take care of ______ in England. She worried that I couldn’t eat or sleep well there",
      options: ["me","myself","her","herself"],
      correct_option: "myself"
  },
  {
      question: "The paint on the wall is not as ______ as it was ten years ago. It has changed from white to gray",
      options: ["bright","heavy","sure","young"],
      correct_option: "bright"
  },
  {
      question: "I told you this road went the wrong way, but you just wouldn’t listen. Now we have to ______ and take another road",
      options: ["go ahead","move away","pass by","turn back"],
      correct_option: "turn back"
  },
  {
      question: "The last five years have not been ______ to Jennie. Her face is covered with lines and she looks much older than she is",
      options: ["kind","special","real","enough"],
      correct_option: "kind"
  },
  {
      question: "My dog Jimmy loves ______ with a comb. Every time I comb his hair, he will close his eyes and fall asleep",
      options: ["to brush","brushing","to be brushing","being brushed"],
      correct_option: "being brushed"
  },
]
